Guide to the David Skorton papers, 2006-2015.
Skorton, David papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
David Skorton papers, 2006-2015.
3-15-3697
Skorton, David J.
18 cubic feet.
Correspondence, reports.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, reports, subject files, background material, and other records relating to Skorton's Presidency of Cornell University.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
President of Cornell University, 2006-2015.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, reports, subject files, background material, and other records relating to Skorton's Presidency of Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Skorton, David J.; Cornell University -- Administration.; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University. President.
Subjects:
Universities and colleges -- Accreditation.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin. Consult the University Archivist. Restriction reviews may take up to a month for completion.
CONTAINER LIST
- Undergraduate Student Handbook, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- China Brochure, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Biomedical Engineering, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Black Students United, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bus Passes, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Campus Code of Conduct, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Campus Code of Conduct, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Conversation with Shimon Perez, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Cornell Police v. Peace Officers, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Council for the Arts, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Darfur, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Darfur, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Darfur, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Darfur, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Diversity Council, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Diversity Council, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cornell University Economic Impact on New York State, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Cornell University Economic Impact on New York State, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 17a)
- Faculty on Ithaca and Weill Campus, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Faculty Senate, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Foundation Relations, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Foundation Relations-Melon Foundation, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Gates, Bill, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Google, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Houghton, Amo, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- House Committee on Science and Technology, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- India, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Intellectual Property - McGovern Report, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- June Alcohol Summit, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- KyotoNow, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- National Collegiate Athletic Association, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- New York Academy of Sciences, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Pataki - Governor, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- President's Summit Meeting, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- President's Council of Cornell Women, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Qatar Bio Bank, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Skorton Global Health Panel, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Slope Day - Offensive T-shirt, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Social Sciences External Advisory Council, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Technology Transfer Steering Committee, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- University of Houston, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- University of Houston, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Virginia Tech Tragedy, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Weill Cornell Medical College Purchase SAP System, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Energy Recovery Linac Roll-out, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Biomed Engineering, Neurological Surgery Research Dedication, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Skorton Web Welcome, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Judith Butler Lecture, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- BOCES Visit, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Peter Karp Retirement, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Iscol Lecture Invitation, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Affirmative Action Statement, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Cornell Daily Sun Column, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Animal Health Diagnostic Center - Pataki Visit, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Cornell Silicon Valley Welcome, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Fleming Dinner, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Alumni Directory Quotation, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- New Student Convocation Ideas, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- New Student Reading - Great Gatsby, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Inaugural Schedule, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Reunion Kick-Off, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 911 Commemorative, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Presidential Councillor Dinner and Welcome, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Bowers Professorship, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Alumni Affairs and Development Presentation, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Society for the Humanities, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Arts and Sciences Advisory Council, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Heart House Gala, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Forum for Undergraduate Student Editors 2006 Conference, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Cornell Daily Sun Column, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- University Faculty Committee Meeting, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Atkinson Forum Dinner, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Engineering Fall Reception, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Employee Recognition Luncheon, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Miller Dinner Greenwich - West Chester, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Diversity Magazine, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Local Leader Brunch, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Cornell Daily Sun Column, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Major Gifts Committee, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- President's Circle, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Peter Kuniholm Conference, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Big Red Big Spirit Celebration, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- United Way, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Kay Hall Dedication, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Awards, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Schoellkopf Dedication, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Irvin Mayfield, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Stephen Ashley Lunch, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Sandy Weill Keynote Introduction, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Campaign Celebration, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Trustee-Council Weekend, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Cornell Annual Fund, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Alumni Affairs and Development Pep Rally, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- 400 Club Brakfast, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Chronicle of Higher Education - The Google Syndrome, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine Article Due, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Weiss/ Lynch Visit, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Hatfield Lecture - Irwin Jacobs, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Konvitz Lecture, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Hatfield Dinner, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Sy Katz Parade, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Chui and Schaepe Dinner, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Cornell Silicon Valley Advisors, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Hays Clark Memorial, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Christopher Reeves Celebration, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Simon Perez, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Images of Cornell End Piece, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Einaudi Center Lunch, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Alpha Phi Alpha, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Leadership Dinner, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Cornell Cooperative Extension, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Ithaca Downtown Partnership Dinner, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Tisch Power Breakfast, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Washington DC Reception, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Winter Commencement, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Miscellaneous Projects, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- India, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Kintner Meeting re: Hotline, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- ICRISAT, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Bangalore, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Mumbai, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Delhi, India, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Ezra Cornell 200th Birthday Statement, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- "Business of Higher Education Financing" Opening Remarks, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Ithaca Cardiology Policy Conference, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Grand Rounds, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Cornell Association of Class Officers Mid-winter Meeting, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Life Sciences Advisory Council, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- President's Circle, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Ambulatory Care Emergency, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Mike Abrams Professorship, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Robert Moses Introduction, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Cornell Daily Sun - Internationalization of Cornell, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine Article Due, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Committee on Special Education Programs Meeting, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Academic Assembly of Libraries, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Senior Class Campaign Kick-Off, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Einaudi Lecture Intro - Roderick Floy, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Faculty Senate, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Cornell Association of Professor Emeriti Lecture, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Cornell Club of Sarasota - Manatee, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Harris Dinner, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Pillsbury Dinner, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Kaplan Dinner, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Investment Committee, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Ithaca Rotary, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- ROTC Faculty Appreciation, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Black Students United Forum, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Cornell Daily Sun Article - Mental Health, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Assemblies Leadership Breakfast, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Miscellany Quotes and Statements - January and February, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Law School Advisory Council, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Chronicle of Higher Education article "Courting a Subcontinent, a Whirlwind Tour of India by Cornell's President", 2007-03-02 (Box 3, Folder 28A)
- Intro to LaFeber Last Lecture, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Human Services Coalition, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Academic State of University Address, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Noyes Community Recreation Center, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Ezra Cornell Birthday, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Distinguished Chair Holders with trustees, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine Article Due - Sustainability, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- President's Council of Cornell Women, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Los Angeles All Alumni, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- West Coast Tower Club, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Cornell Silicon Valley, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Global Health Conference, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Cook Award Letter, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Perkins Prize, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Entrepreneur of the Year Award - Kevin McGovern, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Virginia Tech Op Ed, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Emerging Market Symposium, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Latino Studies Lunch, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Johnson School Hall of Honor, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Bob Swieringa Dinner, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Office Professionals Symposium, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Kaplan Lecture - Nick Kristoff, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Biomedical Engineering Lecture, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Advisory Council, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Parents Campus Visit, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Hoy Field Dedication, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Atkinson Forum, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Retiring Faculty, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Tower Club Dinner - NYC, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Partnership for NYC, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Ira and Gale Drukier Foremost Benefactor, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Distinguished Faculty Reception, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Memorial Sloan-Kettering Academic Convocation, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Lehman Brothers, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Biomed Engineering Advisory Council, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Dana Foundation, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Law School Convocation, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Staff Graduation, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Student Services Staff, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine article Due, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Merrill Presidential Scholars, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Senior Convocation - Soledad O'Brien Introduction, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Milstein Naming, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Senior Class Campaign, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Board of Trustees, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- PhD Ceremony, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Newly Tenured Faculty Awards Dinner, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Commencement, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Weill Cornell Medical College Commencement, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Op Ed - Marshall Plan, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Bibliowicz Dinner, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Commencement Ushers Reception, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Service Recognition Dinner, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Reunion - Oldest Classes Reception, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Reunion - Olin Lecture - Jim Bell, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Reunion - Class of 1952, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Reunion - Class of 1972, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Reunion - Class of 1982, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Reunion - Class of 1977, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 89)
- Reunion - Class of 1962, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Reunion - Class of 1957, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 91)
- State of the University Address, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Tanner Prize - A. Tisch, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Gift Announcement (Weill $25 Million - Institute of Cell and Molecular Biology), 2007 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- New Board of Trustee Orientation, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Cornell Club of London, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Mary Opperman Tribute, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Israeli Boycott Statement, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Miscellany questions, Projects, Letters, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Globalization Conference, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Johnson School Advisory Council, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Cornell Center for Technology, Enterprise and Commercialization, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Parents Reception, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Advisory Council, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Body Map Exhibit Opening, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Milman Professorship, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Lakhdar Brahimi Introduction, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Lynch Professorship Dedication, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Sarah Thomas Farewell, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Joe Solmonese Introduction, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Steve Sinoisky Lecture, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Parents Fund Committee, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- President's Council of Cornell Women, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Bartels Lecture, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Bob Swieringa Dinner, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- East Campus Research Facility, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Article 129a Compliance, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Campus Code of Conduct, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Compos Mentis The First Season-CD, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Education City Presidents, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Faculty Senate, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Judge Raid Juhi Hamadi Al-Saedi (Law School), 2007 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Marshall Plan, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Mellon Foundation, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- National Collegiate Athletic Association, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- New World Order - General Zinni (Rhodes Lecturer) - CD, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- New York Sea Grant, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Positioning Cornell University as a Leader in the 21st Century, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- President's Advisory Committee on Voluntary System of Accountability, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Say Yes, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Senior Leadership Planning Retreat, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- SUNY Chancellor Search, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- University Diversity Council, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Weill Cornell Medical College - Quatar Agreement, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Weiss Presidential Fellows, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Sustainable Agriculture Education Conference, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Science and Technology Committee Testimony, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Gogo Kiplinger Service, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Affirmative Action Statement, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- New Student Convocation, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Annual Fund Stewardship Letter, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine Article Due, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Lance Student Op Ed, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Graduate Students Orientation, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- New York State Fair, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- TST BOCES, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Study Abroad Welcome Back Reception, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Fall 2007 Priorities, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Ithaca City School District Event, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Chronicle of Higher Education Op Ed - Marshall Plan, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Presidential Councillors, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Consortium of Financing Higher Education, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Faculty Senate, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Alumni Affairs and Development Kick-Off, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Tracktenberg Book Essay, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Closing the Minority Achievement Gap in Higher Education, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Geneva 125th Anniversary, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Dan and Muffy Miller Dinner, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Hanan Ashrauri Lecture - Introduction, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- School of Hotel Administration 8th Birthday, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Wilderness Medical Conference, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Agriculture and Information Systems Welcome, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Employee Week Address, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Tri-Institutional-Weill Cornell - Rockefeller - Sloan-Kettering Program, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Tri-Institutional Course Ethics, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Tisch Power Breakfast, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Community Leaders Brunch, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine Due, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Dala Lama Introduction, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Bethe House Opening, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Leading Cornell, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Statement on Tolerance, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- School of Industrial and Labor Relations Faculty Reception, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Emergency Notification Thanks, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Lynch - Weiss Event, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Frank H. T. Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Awards, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Eid Al-Fitr, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- NYS Founders City, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Cornell High Energy Synchrotron Source Site Visit, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Meinig Family Scholars, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Rushdie Lunch, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Happy Birthday Ezra, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Trustee Council Sustainability, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Cornell Annual Fund Breakfast, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Asia Cornell Club of Japan, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Asia Cornell Club of Korea, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Asia Cornell Club of Hong Kong, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Asia Cornell Club of Shanghai, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Asia Cornell Club of Beijing, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Counseling and Psychological Services Beide, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Renmin University 70th Anniversary, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Science Technology Engineering Math Undergraduate Education, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Rochester Institute of Technology Inauguration - Destler, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Federoff Document, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Science in the City, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- New York City Symposium at United Nations, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Weill-Cornell Meet and Greet, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Biology Discussion Group with Robin Davisson, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Big Red Hockey Reception, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Biomedical Engineering 411, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Undergraduate Student Handbook, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Park Fellows Reception, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- December Graduates Reception, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Miscellany Projects, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Cornell Club of Sarasota Scholar Reception, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Focus on the Nation Teach-in Letter, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Campaign Celebration, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Committee on Special Education Programs, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Senior Class Campaign Kick-off, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Advancing Sustainability Action Plan Retreat Letter, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Cornell Daily Sun - Graduate, Professional Education, Life, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine Due, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Tisch Power Breakfast, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Cornell Institute for Public Affairs Marshall Plan, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- East Coast Asian American Conference - Letter, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- West Campus Council Talking Points, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Harris Dinner, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Investment Committee, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- All Faculty Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- President's Climate Communication Implementation Committee, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Admitted Students Website, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Miscellany Projected, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Weill Cornell Medical College - Quatar, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Physics Historic Site, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Introduction of Ambassador Salieh, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Chaplains Meeting, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Academic State of the University Address, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- President's Council of Cornell Women, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- General Faculty Council, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Davo Conference, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Clinton Global Initiative Commitment, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Clinton Global Initiative, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Cornell Facilities Professionals, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- President's Circle, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Kendall Reception, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- BioEthics Society, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 81)
- Engineering College Council, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Poverty Then and Now Conference, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Relay for Life, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Miscellany Projects, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Johnson School State of School, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Communicators at Cornell, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- United Way Breakfast, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Cornell Silicon Valley Event, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Introduction of Robert Rotberg, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Milstein Entrepreneur of the Year Award, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Eco Village Westhaven Farm Dinner, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Cornell Alumni Magazine-Divesity Hosting, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Croll Dinner, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Mortar Board Last Lecture, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- United Way Video, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- International Student Reception, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Cook Awards Welcome, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Service Clubs Banquet, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Cornell University Financial Forum, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Health Career Lecture, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Parents Campus Visit, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Nina Federoff-Building Global United States, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- NYC Tower Club, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Miscellany projects, letters, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Robert Harris Reception, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Weill Cornell Medical College-Qatar, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- End of Year Email, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Distinguished Faculty Awards, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- David Wippman Reception, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Johnson Museum Ground Breaking, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- China Visit, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Merrill Presidential Scholars and Dinner, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Animal Health Diagnostic Center Ground Breaking, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Class of 2008 Campaign Reception, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Board of Trustee Dinner-Honoring Charles Walcott, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- PhD Ceremony, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Senior Convocation-Maya Angelou, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Newly Tenured Faculty and Faculty Awards Dinner with Trustees, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Abby and David Cohen Foremost Benefactor, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Commencement Ideas, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Weill Cornell Medical College Commencement, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 43)